Guide to the Brooklyn For Peace records 2016.026
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Events, 1988-2017; 4.48 Linear Feet in 1 and a half manuscript boxes, 7 media boxes and 1 oversize folder.
  - Sub-Series 3B: Event Recordings, 1991-2016
    - Boycott Divestment and Sanctions, Omar Barghouti and Robin Court DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - Brooklyn Law School CD, 2010 (Box 41)
    - Brooklyn Parents for Peace DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - Brooklyn Peace Rally with Yvette Clarke, Nydia Velazquez, David Yassky, and Bill DeBlasio DVD, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Media, History and Late-Breaking News in the Israel-Palestine Conflict at St. Francis College, Full Length DVD, 2007 (Box 43)
    - Brooklyn Society for Ethical Culture and Park Slope Methodist Church Memorial DVD, 2007 (Box 45)
    - Budget Cuts DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - Charlie Horowitz Memorial, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 84)
    - Chase Madar on Chelsea Manning DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Chelsea Manning DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Climate Action DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Climate Action Workshop at Peace Fair, Another world is Possible DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Climate Change DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Climate Change at the Brooklyn Food Conference DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Combatants, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 61)
    - Combatants for Peace Talk DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - Congressman Major Owens at Brooklyn Parents for Peace Fair DVD, 2005 (Box 44)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Harvey Wasserman, Clamshell Alliance and Keku Test Bar, undated (Box 38, Cassette 5)
    - Counter-Recruitment Rap, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 92)
    - Cuba DVD, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Darfur, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 93)
    - Darfur Drumming, undated (Box 39, Cassette 78)
    - Darfur DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - Darfur VHS, undated (Box 40)
    - David Rovicks DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - Death and Taxes DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - DeRay Media VHS, undated (Box 40)
    - Distorting Justice, Israel / Palestine and US Terrorism Law DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Dorothy Day and Cornell West DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Dorothy Nao on the Cost of the Occupation to Israeli and Palestinian Societies DVD, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Dr. Nikhil Singh at Peace Fair DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Drone Forum DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Drone Tour DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Drone Warfare with Ann Wright DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Drones, Full Length DVD, 2012 (Box 42)
    - Drumming for Darfur DVD, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Earth Charter Summit on Climate Crisis at the City College of New York DVD, 2008 (Box 42)
    - Eisenberg on the Arms Race 1945-1986 (Box 38, Cassette 4, Cassette 6)
    - Eisenberg on What Happened in Iceland, 1986 (Box 38, Cassette 8)
    - Egyptian Revolution, Gaza, Arab Spring, and New Middle East DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Energy Democracy with Sean Sweeney and Kim Fraczek, Question and Answer DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Evan London, Killing of Crows, undated (Box 38, Cassette 2)
    - Father Roy Bourgeois at Peace Fair DVD, 2010 (Box 43, Box 42)
    - Forum on Afghanistan with Fitzgerald and Gould DVD, 2009 (Box 44)
    - Food Conference, Brooklyn Food Coalition DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Forum on Afghanistan DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Forum on Haiti DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - Forum on the Nakba CD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Frackonomics, Myths and Lies, Deborah Lawrence at the Energy Policy Forum DVD, 2013 (Box 42)
    - Framework of International Law DVD, 2010 (Box 41)
    - Grace Paley DVD, undated (Box 42, Box 43)
    - Gaza, Mat Ajl DVD, 2010 (Box 42)
    - Gaza Report Back, Full Length DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - Gaza Report Back DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - Graduate Center, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 95)
    - GroundZero Television, Washington D.C. 2005 and Other Things DVD (Box 44)
    - Guns in America DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Hanan Ashrawi on The US Role in the Middle East Peace Process DVD, 2004 (Box 42)
    - Howard Zinn on War and the Election DVD, 2004 (Box 45)
    - Haiti Forum DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - Howard Zinn DVD, 2004 (Box 42)
    - Howard Zinn DVD, undated (Box 41)
    - Howard Zinn on War and The Election, 2004 (Box 39, Cassette 73)
    - Howard Zinn Tape 2, 2004 (Box 38, Cassette 27)
    - Howard Zinn Tape 7, 2004 (Box 38, Cassette 18)
    - Howard Zinn VHS, undated (Box 40)
    - International Law Session 1 with Peter Weiss and Jeanne Mirer DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - International Law Session 2 DVD, 2010 (Box 41)
    - Invisible Ballots DVD, undated (Box 43)
    - Iran, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 63)
    - Iran After a Nuclear Agreement DVD, 2015 (Box 42)
    - Iran, Confrontation or Diplomacy? DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Iran DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Iran Forum DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Iran, Manufactured Crisis with Gareth Porter DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Iran Panel VHS, 2006 (Box 40)
    - Iran, The Next War? DVD, undated (Box 43)
    - Iraq Developments, 1992 (Box 38, Cassette 9)
    - Iraq Vets DVD, 2006 (Box 43)
    - Iraq War Veterans VHS, 2006 (Box 40)
    - Islamophobia and Anti-Muslim Speech, Jews against Islamophobia DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Israel-Palestine, Raw Footage, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 101)
    - Israeli Apartheid Week 2012, NYU Students for Justice in Palestine DVD (Box 41)
    - Israeli Talk, Dorothea, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 24, Box 39, Cassette 74)
    - Jack Ross DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Jeremy Scahill on America's Covert Wars at Peace Fair DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Juan Gonzalez at Peace Fair DVD, 2011 (Box 41)
    - Lovely Lively Lyrical Ladies Concert DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Macia Kannry and Rev. Khader DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Madea Benjamin, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 90)
    - Mahmoud Abbas at the Cooper Union DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - March on Schumer VHS, 2006 (Box 40)
    - Marx Returns DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Media, History and Late-Breaking News in the Israel-Palestine Conflict DVD, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Medical Effects of Nuclear Weapon in Iraq, undated (Box 38, Cassette 12)
    - Military Myths, Original Version DVD, undated (Box 44)
    - Middle East Forum DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Mosa Sabatello, Human Rights in Gaza and the Occupied Territories, Full Length, Unedited DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Music on the Barge Tape 1, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 58)
    - Nakba Forum DVD, 2008 (Box 44, Box 43)
    - NATO DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - No Nukes DVD, 2009 (Box 43)
    - NSA Listening Party, Presented by Charity Case and Brooklyn For Peace DVD, undated (Box 43)
    - Nuclear-Free Forum DVD, 2015 (Box 42)
    - Nuclear Nightmare DVD, 2015 (Box 42)
    - Nuclear Soviet Union, 1991 (Box 38, Cassette 15)
    - Nuclear Zero DVD, 2009 (Box 43)
    - Nuclear Zero DVD, 2011 (Box 41)
    - Nukes Part 2, Cuba DVD, undated (Box 44)
    - NYU Students for Justice in Palestine with Jared Malsin and Chris Hedges DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Omar Barghouti at NYU DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Operation Desert Calm: March on the White House, Operation Real Security VHS, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Original Performer Showcase CD, 2008 (Box 44)
    - P.P.W. Carroll Park, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 67)
    - Palestinian Nakba and Israel Independence Day DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - Palestinian Nakba and Israeli Independence Day with Maya Wind and Eran Efrati DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Panla Broll, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 91)
    - Pathmakers to Peace DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Pathmakers to Peace with Noam Chomsky DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Pathmakers to Peace DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Pathmakers to Peace with Michael Ratner DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Paul Chappell at the Peace Fair DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Peace Fair, 2008 (Box 39, Cassette 98)
    - Peace Fair DVD, 2006 (Box 42, Box 43, Box 45)
    - Peace Fair DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Peace Fair DVD, 2010 (Box 42)
    - Peace Fair Interview DVD, 2005 (Box 43)
    - Peace Fair Full Length Unedited DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Peace Fair Opening DVD, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Peace Fair Opening VHS, 2004 (Box 40)
    - Peace Fair Performer Showcase DVD, 2008 (Box 44)
    - Peace Fair VHS, 2006 (Box 40)
    - Peace Fair Raw Footage, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 31, Box 39, Cassette 103)
    - Peace and Planet DVD, 2015 (Box 43)
    - Peace and Planet DVD, 2015 (Box 42)
    - Peace and Planet with Joseph Gerson DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - Peace for Cuba, 1992 (Box 38, Cassette 13)
    - Peace Parade, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 66)
    - Peace Rally, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 69)
    - Phyllis Bennis DVD, 2006 (Box 44)
    - Phyllis Bennis, David Wildman on Syria, Isis, and Refugees: What Can be Done? DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Phyllis Bennis on the Arab Spring, Full Length DVD, 2011-2011 (Box 41)
    - Plemary Peace Fair, undated (Box 39, Cassette 77)
    - Question and Answer with Jared Malsin and Chris Hedges DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Rashid Khalidi - US Undermines Peace in Middle East at Columbia University DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Refugees Forum DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Resistance and Revolution in Gaza, Egypt, Gaza, Arab Spring, and New Middle East DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Rise of the Right, Chip Berlet DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Sean Bell Case DVD, undated (Box 43)
    - Sean Bell Forum, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 19)
    - Seeking Justice and Speaking Truth, Khalil Gibran DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Seeking Peace, Report of the Presbyterian Peacemaking Trip to the Middle East DVD, 2006 (Box 43)
    - Seus Tape, undated (Box 38, Cassette 28)
    - Seymour Melman, 1992 (Box 38, Cassette 14)
    - Solar, Exaggeration of Iraq Militia, undated (Box 38, Cassette 11)
    - Soldiers Injured with Ann Junel - They were Soldiers DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - South African Nuclear Policy, Keku Escalation Dominance, Keku Test Bar, undated (Box 38, Cassette 10)
    - Susan, Storytelling and Closing Remarks, undated (Box 38, Cassette 30)
    - St. Francis, Latin America Question and Answer, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 81)
    - Stop and Frisk Forum DVD, 2013 (Box 42)
    - Story Corps Original, Charlotte Phillips Interview CD, 2008 (Box 45)
    - Student Activism 1960's to 2016 DVD (Box 42)
    - Syria, Isis, and Refugee Crisis with Bennis and Wildman DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Trans Pacific Partnership DVD, 2013 (Box 41, Box 42)
    - The Terror Factory, FBI, and the Manafort War on Terror at Columbia DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Tax Day Forum DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Thomas Hearing, 2016 (Box 38, Cassette 7)
    - Tree of Life DVD, 2012 (Box 41)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 39, Cassette 83)
    - Unidentified #2, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 97)
    - Unidentified Tape #2, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 59)
    - Unidentified Pictures CD, undated (Box 44)
    - Unidentified, Sony Tape #1, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 60)
    - Untitled, January 29, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 17)
    - US Responds to the Islamic State DVD, 2015 (Box 42)
    - Vincent Intondi, African-Americans Against the Bomb DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Walking the Walk with Macia Kannry and Rev. Khader DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - War in Afghanistan with Christian Parenti DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - War Vets Back, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 70)
    - Where are Tax Dollars Going?, Mark Dunler and Mike Zweig Question and Answer DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Women's chorus, Major Owens, Matthew Lev, Rusti and Dixie, undated (Box 38, Cassette 29)
    - Workshops, Morty, Code, 2006 (Box 39, Cassette 89)
    - Workshops, Women's chorus, undated (Box 39, Cassette 76)
    - World Can't Wait - Gaza with Poppe, Kuttub, and Pelod DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Yugoslavia Initiation with DoBol, 1992 (Box 38, Cassette 16)
    - Zarhid Khaludu on Peace in Middle East DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
- Series 4: War No More Program, 2006-2012; 0.5 Linear Feet in 1 media box
  War No More is a monthly television program produced by Brooklyn For Peace, and screened on the public access network Brooklyn Free Speech (BRIC channel 2). The show has aired since 2006, and includes interviews, event recordings and in-depth discussions of local, national and international political issues.
  Material is arranged in episode order, with un-numbered recordings appearing at the end of the series.
  - Episode 1 - Military Myths, 2006 (Box 38, Cassette 32)
  - Episode 2 - Anti-Militarism Panel, 2006 (Box 38, Cassette 33)
  - Episode 3 - Darfur Program, 2006 (Box 38, Cassette 34)
  - Episode 6 - Darfur: What You Can Do, 2006 (Box 38, Cassette 35)
  - Episode 7 - Phyllis Bennis, 2006 (Box 38, Cassette 36)
  - Episode 8 - Unidentified, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 37)
  - Episode 10 - Peace Fair, 2006 (Box 38, Cassette 38)
  - Episode 11 - Combatants For Peace, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 39)
  - Episode 12 - Military Myths, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 40)
  - Episode 13 - Peace Rally and Charlotte Phillips, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 41)
  - Episode 14 - War No More: Dorothy Naos, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 42)
  - Episode 15 - Drumming for Darfur in Prospect Park, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 43)
  - Episode 16 - Charlotte Philips and Alice Rothchild, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 44)
  - Episode 20 - No War Against Iran, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 104)
  - Episode 21 - Media, History, and Late-Breaking News in the Israel-Palestine Conflict, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 105)
  - Episode 22 - Boro Hall, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 106)
  - Episode 23 - Unidentified, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 45)
  - Episode 24 - Seeking Justice- Speaking Truth, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 46)
  - Episode 25 - Iran - The Next War, 2008 (Box 39, Cassette 107)
  - Episode 26 - Walking the Walk, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 47)
  - Episode 31 - Parent, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 48)
  - Episode 32 - Sean Bell Forum, 2008 (Box 38, Cassette 23)
  - Episode 33 - Apartheid from South Africa to Palestine, 2008 (Box 39, Cassette 108)
  - Episode 34 - Abrahammer on Iran, 2008 (Box 39, Cassette 025)
  - Episode 35 - Greg Grandin, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 49)
  - Episode 37 - Charlotte Phillips on Latin America, 2007 (Box 38, Cassette 50)
  - Episode 38, 2009 (Box 39, Cassette 026)
  - Episode 39 - Nakba, 2009 (Box 38, Cassette 51)
  - Episode 40 - Requiem for W, 1-2, 2009 (Box 39, Cassette 99)
  - Episode 42 - Afghanistan, 2009 (Box 38, Cassette 52)
  - Episode 44 - Tom Hayden, 2009 (Box 38, Cassette 53)
  - Episode 45 - Tom Hayden, 2009 (Box 38, Cassette 54)
  - Episode 46 - C.S.A Program, 2010 (Box 38, Cassette 55)
  - Episode 47 - Afghan War, 2009 (Box 38, Cassette 57)
  - Episode 47 - Gaza Report, 2010 (Box 38, Cassette 56)
  - Episode 48 - Nuclear Zero, 2010 (Box 38, Cassette 21)
  - Episode 49 - Nuclear Zero, 2010 (Box 38, Cassette 22)
  - Tom Hayden DVD, 2009 (Box 43, Box 44)
  - War No More: Boycott and Divestment, Replacement for BCAT DVD, 2012 (Box 43)
- Series 5: Subject Files, 1986-2017; 7 Linear Feet in 13 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box.
  This series includes material from a wide range of political organizations and individuals at the local, regional, national and international levels working on issues of interest to BFP. Material in this series consists primarily of publicity mailings and event ephemera, although there is a small amount of correspondence. Subjects that are well represented in this series include BFP's core issues of anti-war and militarism, nuclear disarmament, and the Israel-Palestine conflict. Other topics include racial justice in New York City, abolition, police brutality, and the conflict in Darfur, Sudan.
  Materials have been grouped by subject and arranged alphabetically.
  - 9/11 Coalition for Constitutional and Human Rights, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Afghan War, 2001-2010 (Box 19, Folder 1, Box 37)
  - Abolition 2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Adalah NY The Coalition for Justice in the Middle East, 2009-2013 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Al-Awda Palestine Right of Return Coalition, 2003-2011 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Retired Americans, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 2002-2017 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1986-2009 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Americans for Peace Now, 2006-2010 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - American Jewish World Service, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - American Public Health Association, 2001-2017 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Amnesty International, circa 2008 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Defamation League, circa 2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Anti-War for the Million Worker March, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Arab American Association of New York, 2006-2013 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - The Arab American Family Support Center, Inc, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Art Events in New York City, 2003-2016 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - The Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Better Brooklyn Community Center, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Black Veterans for Social Justice, 2003-2017 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Boycott, Divestment and Sanctions, 2009-2014 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Boycott, Divestment and Sanctions DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
  - Brooklyn Commons Boycott, 2006-2016 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Community Action Network, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Friends School, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Brooklyn Information and Culture (BRIC), 2009-2017 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn Residents Against Bias-Related Violence, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Brooklyn Organizations, 1988-2016 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Society for Ethical Culture, 2003-2015 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - B'Tselem, 2001-2011 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Clinton, Hillary, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Church Avenue Merchants Black Association, Inc, 2003-2007 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for Peace and Democracy, 2006-2016 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Cassini Space Probe, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - The Center for Anti-Violence Education, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 2002-2013 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Center for Defense, 1999-2001 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Center for Defense Information, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - The Center for Popular Democracy, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Central Brooklyn Independent Democrats, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The Central Brooklyn Martin Luther King Commission, 2014-2018 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Citizens' Committee for Children, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Citizens Defending Libraries, 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Citizen Soldier, 2001-2008 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Civil Liberties After September 11th, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Clarke, Yvette, 2005-2017 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Climate Centered Organizations, 2003-2017 (Box 20, Folder 15, Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Coalition for a Nuclear Free Harbor, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 16, Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Coalition of Concerned Legal Professionals, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Coalition for Veterans in Pain and Distress, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - College and Universities, 1998-2015 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Committee in Solidarity with People of El Salvador, 1991-2011 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Committee for a Nuclear-Free Island, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Committee Opposed to Militarism and the Draft, 2002-2011 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Committee to Honor Eugene Mckenzie, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Restricted until 2031.
  - Congressman Major Owens Peace and Justice Advisory Committee, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Restricted until 2033.
  - Counter Punch, 1999-2012 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Courage to Refuse, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Creative Response to Conflict, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Culture Project, 2003-2013 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Defenders for Freedom, Justice, and Equality, circa 2010 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Darfur Organizations, 2007-2010 (Box 21, Folder 7, Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Darfur People's Association, 2007-2008 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Darfur, Sudan, 2007-2010 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Democracy Notes, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Genocide in Darfur: What You Can Do to Help, 3 DVDs, 2006 (Box 44)
  - Department of Peace Campaign, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - The Dialogue Project, 2012-2014 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Doctors Without Borders, 2005-2015 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Desis Rising Up and Moving - DRUM, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Educators for Social Responsibility, 1989-2002 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Emergency USA Life Support for Civilian War Victims, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - End the Occupation, 2000-2010 (Box 21, Folder 15, Box 37, Folder 6)
  - The World Says NO! to Israeli Occupation / US Campaign to End the Israeli Occupation DVD, 2007 (Box 43)
  - Environment and Climate, 2011-2014 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Families United for Radical and Economic Equality - FUREE, 2004-2014 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Federal Government, 2000-2016 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation - FOR, 2000-2009 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - First Unitarian Congregational Society, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Food and Water Watch, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Bases Project, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Fort Greene Peace, 2010-2012 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - The Foundation Center, 1987-1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Fracking, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Freedom Legal Defense and Education Project, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Freedom Party, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1999-2002 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Girls Educational and Mentoring Services - GEMS, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Global Exchange, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The Granny Peace Brigade, 2010-2015 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Grassroots Leadership, 1983-1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Green Party of Brooklyn, 2010-2011 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Gulf War, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hamoked Center for the Defence of the Individual, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Healthcare Centered Organizations, 1991-2006 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - High School for Civil Rights, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Homeport, Staten Island, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Ifetayo Cultural Arts Facility, Inc., 2006 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Independent Progressive Politics Network - IPPN, 2003-2011 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - InFact, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - International Action Center, 1991-2006 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - International A.N.S.W.E.R Coalition, 2003-2009 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - International Campaign to Abolish Nuclear Weapons - ican, 2010-2015 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - International Centered Organizations, 1991-2008 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - International Coalition to Ban Uranium Weapons - ICBUM, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - International Justice Project, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, 2000-2010 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Iran, 2007-2014 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Iran Centered Organizations, 2011-2014 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Iraq Centered Organizations, 1991-2008 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Iraq Veterans Against the War, 2012-2015 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Iraq War, 2000-2007 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Israel - Palestine, 2001-2015 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Restricted until 2045.
  - Israel - Palestine Organizations, 2003-2016 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Israeli School Books DVD, undated (Box 42)
  - Japan Association of Lawyers Against Nuclear Arms - JALANA, 2009-2014 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Jeffries, Hakeem, 2013-2015 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Alliance for Justice and Peace, 2005-2008 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Voice for Peace, 2002-2013 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Jews Against Islamophobia JAIC - Jews Say NO!, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Jews against Islamophobia, Anti Muslim Speech Hate Speech DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
  - Justice Coalition for Alberta Spruill and Ousmane Zongo, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Justice for Detainees, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Khalil Gibran International Academy, 2007-2010 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Kids First, NY, 1999-2000 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Kolot Chayeinu, 2008-2013 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Korean Organizations, 2015-2017 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Kosovo, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - LaGuardia Community College, 2006-2011 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lawyers Committee on Nuclear Policy - LCNP, 1985-2002 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - LEAP, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Long Island Alliance for Peaceful Alternatives, 1997-2015 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Madre Speaks, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - The Martin Luther King, Jr. Center New York Support Group, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 13)